A Guide to the Furious Flower Poetry Center Conference Records, 1970-2015: UA 0018
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
Furious Flower Poetry Center Conference Records,
1970-2015
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
James Madison University. Furious Flower Poetry Center
UA 0018
7.52 cubic feet; 13 hollinger boxes, 1 half-hollinger box, 1 oversize hollinger box, 1 record storage box, 1 rolled storage container
The Furious Flower Poetry Center Conference Records, consisting of 7.52 cubic feet, comprises materials related to the decennial Furious Flower Poetry Center conferences beginning with the inaugural conference in 1994.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection open to research. Currently, the silk banners used in the 2004 and 2014 Furious Flower Poetry Conferences may only be requested (in writing) by Furious Flower Poetry Center staff. Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection. Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the James Madison University Special Collections Library to use this collection.
Acquisition Information
Furious Flower Poetry Center transferred these materials to Special Collections on May 16 and June 29, 2016.
Other Formats Available
Digitization of media content is in-process as of August 2016. Access will be made available to content once digitization is complete, barring any copyright or use restrictions.
Accruals
It is anticipated that the Furious Flower Poetry Center will continue to donate conference files approximately every ten years.
Administrative History
In 1994, James Madison University, under the leadership and direction of professor of English Dr. Joanne V. Gabbin, hosted the first Furious Flower Poetry Conference entitled A Revolution in African American Poetry. This Conference, dedicated to acclaimed poet Gwendolyn Brooks, featured scholars, critics, and the most accomplished and esteemed poets of the time including Nikki Giovanni, Rita Dove, Sonia Sanchez, Michael S. Harper, Haki Madhubuti, and Gwendolyn Brooks herself. The name "Furious Flower" is derived from Brooks' poem Second Sermon on the Warpland in which she writes:
The time cracks into furious flower. Lifts its face all unashamed. And sways in wicked grace.
Many who participated in the inaugural Furious Flower conference had their roots in the Black Arts Movement. The Black Arts Movement emerged in the wake of the Black Power Movement of the 1960s and 1970s and was comprised of politically motivated black visionaries, poets, artists, dramatists, musicians, and writers. Due to the success of the 1994 Furious Flower Conference, the Furious Flower Poetry Center (FFPC) was established in 1999 and the Conference became a decennial event, held every ten years. The subsequent conferences were Regenerating the Black Poetic Tradition (2004) and Seeding the Future of African American Poetry. Conference programming is comprised of concerts, readings, roundtable and panel discussions, and paper presentations.
Scope and Content
The Furious Flower Poetry Center Conference Records, 1970-2015, consisting of 7.52 cubic feet, comprises materials related to the decennial Furious Flower poetry conferences, beginning with the inaugural conference in 1994. A significant portion of the records include logistical and planning documentation for each conference as well as marking and promotional items. These materials are comprised of calls for papers, contracts, correspondence, address lists, ticket requests, travel, transportation, and lodging reservations, and menus. The records include nontraditional items as well. Of interest are exhibit panels (text labels and images) describing and depicting the participants of the 1994 conference. Magnesium letterpress die plates used to print a limited edition portfolio Furious Flower: A Revolution in African American Poetry, a special collection of 23 poems selected by poets (who participated in the 1994 conference) to represent their work, are included. Six silk banners that adorned the Wilson Hall auditorium during the 2004 and 2014 conferences are included.
While there may be overlap in content, materials directly related to general organizational activities of the Furious Poetry Center form a separate collection – Furious Flower Poetry Center Records, UA 0017.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into four series:
Series 1: 1994 Conference, 1970-2009
Series 2: 2004 Conference, 2002-2007
Series 3: 2014 Conference, 2013-2015
Series 4: Media
As a result of their inherent chronological series arrangement, Series 1, 2, and 3 are arranged alphabetically with the exception of the Exhibit of Participants materials and the magnesium letterpress die plates in Series 1 which located at the end of the series due to their size. Series 4: Media has no particular arrangement as the materials are undergoing digitization as of August 2016.
Related Material
Furious Flower Poetry Center Records, 1990-2014, UA 0017, Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University, Harrisonburg, VA.
Separated Material
A broadside printing of Rita Dove's "Ode to My Right Knee" (no. 39 of 100) was removed from the collection and cataloged separately.
Bibliography
"Furious Flower Poetry Center." James Madison University. Accessed August 30, 2016. https://www.jmu.edu/furiousflower/index.shtml.
Index Terms
Subjects:
American poetry -- African American authors; Poetry -- History and criticism; African American poets; African Americans -- Poetry; African Americans -- Intellectual life -- 20th century; African Americans -- Intellectual life -- 21st century; United States -- Poetry; United States -- Intellectual life -- 20th century; United States -- Intellectual life -- 21st century
Genre and Form Terms:
Administrative records; Photographs; Exhibit scripts; Poetry; DVDs; Letters (correspondence); Electronic mail; Posters; Programs (documents); Letterpress printing; Banners
- Series 1: 1994 Conference, 1970-2009
  Scope and Content
  Arranged alphabetically with the exception of the Exhibit of Participants materials and the magnesium letterpress die plates which are located at the end of the series due to their size. Note that the numbering system for the letterpress die plates is sequential based on each poem's order in the publication Furious Flower: A Revolution in African American Poetry. As such the first folder/four-flap enclosure in box nine is labeled 9:21b. This is the plate for page two of the 21st poem in the publication. Materials in this series primarily document the planning and implementation of the 1994 Furious Flower Poetry Conference: A Revolution in African American Poetry. Records include travel and lodging reservations, correspondence with participating poets, financial documentation and budgets, and mailing lists. Marketing and promotional items such as posters and brochures are included. Conference evaluations completed by attendees and folders labeled "Positive Responses" document the overwhelming success of the conference. Of particular interest are exhibit components from the 1994 conference that include text labels and images of each participating poet. The photographs for these panels were taken by C. B. Claiborne. Copy 225 of 300 of Furious Flower: A Revolution in African American Poetry is located in box 2, folder 5. The magnesium letterpress die plates used to print this collection of poetry are also included here. Each plate is individually housed in a four-flap enclosure and then boxed in order of appearance in the publication.
  - 1994 Conference Finances, 1993-2004 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1994 Conference Program, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Addresses, 1991-1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Articles Written/Speeches Given, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bell Atlantic, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Commitments, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Compiled Evaluations - Furious Flower, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Conference - Abstracts Rejected, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Conference Pictures, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Conference Responses, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Conference Working Papers Furious Flower, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - CVs of Various Artists, 1993-2009, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - CVs of Various Artists, 1993-2009, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Ticket Requests, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - FF 1994 conference, 1992-1999, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - FFI DVD and Video, 1998-2009 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - FF: Critics, 1993-1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - FF: Poets, 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Film Documentary, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - "Furious Flower: A Revolution in African American Poetry" Collector's Edition, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Furious Flower Brochure, 1992-1994 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Furious Flower Conference, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Furious Flower Conference Book Exhibit, 1970-1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Furious Flower Conference Fall '93, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Furious Flower Conference Fall '93, 1993-1997 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Furious Flower Conference - Menus, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Furious Flower Conference Transportation & Travel, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Furious Flower Contracts, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Furious Flower Inquiries - to be entered on response, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Furious Flower Revised Master, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Incoming Conference Correspondence, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Invited Guest Travel Preferences, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - JMU Conference Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Mailing Labels, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Master Copies - Tickets, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Media Relations, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Conference Materials (Folder 1 of 3), 1992-1995 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Conference Materials (Folder 2 of 3), 1992-1995 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Conference Materials (Folder 3 of 3), 1992-1995 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Motel/Hotel Accommodations, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Open Mic Furious Flower Poets, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Outgoing Conference Correspondence (Folder 1 of 2), 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Outgoing Conference Correspondence (Folder 2 of 2), 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Patrons, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Photographs, Contact Sheets, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Poetry Project, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Positive Responses - Conference 1994 (Folder 1 of 2), 1994 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Positive Responses - Conference 1994 (Folder 2 of 2), 1994 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Press Furious Flower Conference Fall '93, 1993-2003 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Press Pictures, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Promotional & Event Materials, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 6, Box OV 1, Folder 1)
  - Proposal, Budget, Media Relations, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Publication Permission Slips, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Publications, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 9, Box OV 1, Folder 1)
  - Receivables, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Registration Information, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Remittance, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Requests for Petty Cash Checks, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Schedules and logistics, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Signature Portfolio, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Student Ticket Requests, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Travel Requests, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Volunteers, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Elizabeth Alexander, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Samuel W. Allen, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Alvin Aubert, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Jabari Asim, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Amiri Baraka, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Gerald Barrax, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Joanna M. Braxton, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Gwendolyn Brooks, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Toi Derricotte, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Rita Dove, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Mari Evans, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Joanne V. Gabbin, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Nikki Giovanni, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Exhibit of Participants - General Signs, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Group Photos, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Michael S. Harper, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Joyce Ann Joyce, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Dolores Kendrick, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Pinkie Gordon Lane, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Naomi Long Madgett, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Haki R. Madhubuti, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Exhibit of Participants - E. Ethelbert Miller, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Opal Moore, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Aldon L. Nielsen, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Raymond R. Patterson, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Sterling D. Plumpp, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Arnold Rampersad, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Bernice Johnson Reagon, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Eugene Redmond, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Sonia Sanchez, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Sharon Strange, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Lorenzo Thomas, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Eleanor W. Traylor, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Jerry W. Ward Jr., 1994 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Sherley Anne Williams, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Exhibit of Participants - Val Gray Ward, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 1 Title Page, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 2 Introduction, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 3 Alexander, Elizabeth "After,", 1994 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 4 Allen, Samuel "The Apple Trees in Sussex,", 1994 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 5 Aubert, Alvin "Baptism,", 1994 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 6 Baraka, Amiri "In the Funk World,", 1994 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 7 Barrax, Gerald "Liberation,", 1994 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 8 Braxton, Joanne M. "Zoning,", 1994 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 9 Brooks, Gwendolyn "The Second Sermon on the Warpland,", 1994 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 10 Derricotte, Toi "Boy at the Paterson Falls,"f, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 11 Dove, Rita "The Island Women of Paris,", 1994 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 12 Evans, Mari "I Am A Black Woman,", 1994 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 13 Giovanni, Nikki "Nikki-Rosa,", 1994 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 14a Harper, Michael S. "The Beauty Shell," (plate 1 of 3), 1994 (Box 8, Folder 14a)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 14b Harper, Michael S. "The Beauty Shell," (plate 2 of 3), 1994 (Box 8, Folder 14b)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 14c Harper, Michael S. "The Beauty Shell," (plate 3 of 3), 1994 (Box 8, Folder 14c)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 15 Kendrick, Dolores "Black Women at the Basin,", 1994 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 16 Lane, Pinkie Gordon "Girl at the Window,", 1994 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 17 Madgett, Naomi Long "Reluctant Light,", 1994 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 18 Madhubuti, Haki "Poet: What Ever Happened to Luther?,", 1994 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 19 Miller, E. Ethelbert "Roy Campanella: January, 1958,", 1994 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 20a Patterson, Raymond R. "Letters to a Black Poet," (plate 1 of 2), 1994 (Box 8, Folder 20a)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 20b Patterson, Raymond R. "Letters to a Black Poet," (plate 2 of 2), 1994 (Box 8, Folder 20b)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 21a Plumpp, Sterling D. "Thaba Nchu," (plate 1 of 2), 1994 (Box 9, Folder 1a)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 21b Plumpp, Sterling D. "Thaba Nchu," (plate 2 of 2), 1994 (Box 9, Folder 1b)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 22a Redmond, Eugene B. "Barbequed Cong: or We Laid My Lai Low," (plate 1 of 2), 1994 (Box 9, Folder 2a)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 22b Redmond, Eugene B. "Barbequed Cong: or We Laid My Lai Low," (plate 2 of 2), 1994 (Box 9, Folder 2b)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 23 Sanchez, Sonia "I Have Walked a Long Time,", 1994 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 24a Ward, Jerry W., Jr. "Jazz to Jackson to John," (plate 1 of 3), 1994 (Box 9, Folder 4a)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 24b Ward, Jerry W., Jr. "Jazz to Jackson to John," (plate 2 of 3), 1994 (Box 9, Folder 4b)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - 24c Ward, Jerry W., Jr. "Jazz to Jackson to John," (plate 3 of 3), 1994 (Box 9, Folder 4c)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - Williams, Sherley Anne "Big Red and His Brothers,", 1994 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Magnesium letterpress die plate - Limited Edition Statement, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Series 2: 2004 Conference, 2002-2007
  Arranged alphabetically.
  Materials in this series primarily document the planning and implementation of the 2004 Furious Flower Poetry Conference: Regenerating the Black Poetic Tradition. Records include travel and lodging reservations, correspondence with participating poets, financial documentation and budgets, and mailing lists. Marketing and promotional items such as posters and brochures are included. During the 2004 conference, notable African American scholars including Tony Bolden, Hilary Holladay, and Monifa Love conducted interviews with presenting conference poets including Houston Baker, Rita Dove, and Tony Medina. The corresponding transcripts are included and are particularly significant to African American poetry scholarship. Of particular interest is congratulatory correspondence and RSVP regrets for the 2004 conference from Julian Bond, Governor Mark Warner, Senator George Allen, the office of President George W. Bush and Senator John Kerry, President and CEO of the NAACP Kweisi Mfume, and many others. Some of these letters were printed in the official conference program. Also of interest are evaluations completed by conference attendees. Six silk banners used to decorate the Wilson Hall auditorium during the conference are included in this series. The banners are rolled onto dowels and housed in a rolled storage container. Currently, the silk banners may only be requested (in writing) by Furious Flower Poetry Center staff.
  - 2004 Arts Council of the Valley Grant, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - 2004 Conference Bills, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - 2004 Conference Contract Letters, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 2004 Conference Finances, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - 2004 Conference VCA Grant, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - The Charles Lafitte Foundation Grant, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Conference Banners, 2004 (Rolledstorage 1)
  - Facilities, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - FF 2004 Budget: Check Deposits, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - FF 2004 Budget: Check and Cash Deposits, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - FF 2004 Budget: Web Deposits, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - FF 2004 Conference Correspondence, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - FF 2004 Essays, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - FF Accommodations, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - FF African American Theatrical Ensemble (AATE), 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - FF Barnes and Noble, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - FF Bibliography, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - FF Call for Papers, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - FF Dignitaries, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - FF Evaluations, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - FF Letters Post Conference, 2004-2005 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - FF Media Clips 2004, 2004-2006 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - FF Musical Venues, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - FF Poster 2004, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 1, Box OV 1)
  - Programs, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - FF Room Reservations, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - FF Steering & Planning Committee Minutes, 2002-2004 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - FF Talent Release Forms (Misc.), 2004 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - FF Transportation, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - FF Vendors, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - FFII DVD, 2004-2005 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Furious Flower Poets, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Furious Flower Quilt, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Interview Transcripts I, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Interview Transcripts II, undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Monthly Detail Reports, 2004-2005 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Mounted Photographs, 2004 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities Grant (1 of 2), 2004 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 13, Box OV 1, Folder 2)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities Grant (2 of 2), 2004 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Promotional and Event Materials, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Review FFII DVD, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - VIA International, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Virginia Commission for the Arts Grant, 2004-2005 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Series 3: 2014 Conference, 2013-2015
  - 2014 Conference Food, 2014 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - 2014 Conference Program, 2014 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - 2014 Conference Releases, 2013-2015 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - 2014 Conference Remarks, 2014, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - 2014 Conference Schedule, 2014, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - 2014 Conference Thank-Yous, 2014, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - 2014 Conference Vouchers, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Advertising, 2013 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Art Exhibits, 2014, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Budget and Workshops, 2013-2015 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Call for Papers, 2014 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Catering, 2014 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Committees, 2013-2014 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Conference Bags-Inserts, 2013-2014, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Conference Evaluations, 2014 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Conference Presenters, 2014, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Conference Promotion, 2014 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Conference Registration (1 of 2), 2014 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Conference Registration (2 of 2), 2014 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - E-Commerce, 2013, 2014 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Ephemera and Tote Bag, 2014, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Exhibitions, 2014 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Facilities, 2014, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Hotel Blocks, 2013, 2014 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Invited Speaker Accommodations (1 of 2), 2014 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Invited Speaker Accommodations (2 of 2), 2014 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Lifetime Achievement Awards, 2013, 2014, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Media Articles, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Obama Letter and Photo, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Performances, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Poet Dialogues, 2014, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Posters, 2013, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Requests to Speak, 2013, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Transportation, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Video Producer, 2013, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Series 4: Media
  Contents
  No particular arrangement.
  All media is in the process of being digitized as of August 2016. Access to content will be made available once digitization is complete, barring any copyright or other use restrictions.